[Music]  is  [Music]  is  [Music]  hey i was listening to that  don't care plus you're a woman  yet put your socks on mom wants us to  walk down to the store to buy some whole  milk and a box of granola bars  right now  it's totally pouring like [ __ ] outside  plus i have a quiz at school tomorrow i  don't have the time  go buy your fat self  let go  they don't vaton hedgehog ears anyway  mom manic broke my new headphones can i  have a hundred and forty five dollars  again  sonia you know i don't have the money to  keep throwing away like that  here's two dollars go buy yourself some  gummy worms instead i don't want that i  want headphones two only two dollars  cheap [ __ ]  bart levy would never  maybe if one of you little shits moved  out or got a job you could afford to buy  your own things but as long as you live  under my roof i make all the demands  we understand the words coming out of  your mouth our purple mother  but you must realize that just because  we are your kids it doesn't mean we are  babies anymore  we have wants and needs and it doesn't  give you the right to deny us our  happiness  heed my bros words we are the next  generation and it's your duty to prop us  up into becoming fine young men and  members of society  okay i don't know why you had to go and  do that  i noticed you two didn't get slapped  today  it's your fault for always running that  sassy mouth of yours baby bro  you know how mom's always on edge when  it's humid like this  why don't you put that mouth to better  use like on my balls  haha haha come on bro you know i was  only joking dang bro anyone tell you  your cheeks be looking like two big  brussels sprouts  hey sips look it's one of those weird  [ __ ] bosses that drive around town  what you say we make the most out of  this outing by making fun of kids with  disabilities  manic what the [ __ ] that won't be fun at  all how would you like it to have  someone made fun of you  haha i'd like to see those losers try  they'll be messing with the hot [ __ ]  where is my double digit iq fellas at  who wants to eat crayons with me tonight  seriously  this is so not cool man go be a poopy  diaper of a person somewhere else it's  my brother's birthday and i'll have you  know we're just returning home  from a round of mini golf unfortunately  it had to be mini golf because my bro is  [ __ ] for the real thing  but i still had fun because it was with  him now leave before i get mad at you  i'm not going to ask twice  it is happening again my brother meanies  are picking on me again  why is the world so dark and cruel does  god wish for me to live in a world  without light  i'm not gonna stick around and watch  this i'll meet you guys on the head  come on bro let's go home and watch  power rangers while we eat your ice  cream cake  and i [ __ ] your hair yes come on [ __ ]  why are you ignoring me like that  don't tell me you're deaf too  [ __ ]  get away your breath smells like ranch  flavored burrito chips yo you better cut  it out real quick  i'm only going to give you seven more  chances to leave my brother alone  how about taste of my beef ravioli  [Music]  [Applause]  [Music]  bro please let me help you get that  rusty knife out of your butt  leave it leave me and catch those goons  they cannot be allowed to flee from this  spot  nice going bro you let them get away  maybe i should beat your ass too bro  just stop beating people up doesn't make  you a badass it doesn't  no in fact all it does is make you a  bully  well that is just factually wrong  what am i doing wasting time talking  with you someone like you would never  understand  unlike you sonic i know the evil of the  world all too well  dad can i have a bite of that girl  what oh you mean the pastry i thought  you meant the thing between my legs for  a second  manic my boy i gave you food three days  ago you don't need food right now my boy  but i'm so hungry i haven't eaten for  three days  fine but listen up my boy if you want a  bike you're gonna have to do something  for me first  you see that to risk to crack over there  daddy doesn't have the money for  cigarettes go over there and snatch 13  or  1254 dollars from him  do that and i'll rub some of the  cinnamon dust from the churro into your  hand that you can lick  but farrell that man is walking with  crutches should i really  why do you always only want me stealing  from the crippled  surely there's better fish to fry  oh um i just i thought that sealing from  crippled people would be  a good way for you to learn before you  handle the big guns  like normal people  [Music]  mother of god what do you think you're  doing back there with my wallet  no i wasn't i was only  silence do you have the slightest clue  who i happen to be  i'm of the montclair family and in one  year's time me and my twin brother  butler be montclair of resident will  have about to the death and the one who  comes out alive will receive our  family's fortune once that happens i'll  be the richest man on mobius and you'll  be [ __ ] dead  police police hurry here somebody call  the cop  mobian police department the best in the  force at your service what happens to be  the problem here  hurry up and grab him then lock him up  in the mobian slave camps  feral help me don't let them take me  again  feral wait dad come back  daddy daddy don't leave me  [Music]  enjoy your last meal before being locked  away in a concentration camp  this is more than what a ruffian like  you deserve  [Music]  hey do you know where the raisin granola  bars are at  all 12 you can't miss it thanks for  choosing to shop at your local walmart  okay thanks  howdy sir is there anything i can't help  you with  don't make a move and don't make the  sound [ __ ] just put the money in the  bag if you don't want things to get  messy  but you're not carrying a bag [ __ ]  [ __ ] i forgot  okay put the money in the wait  hey employee guy are those security  cameras actually on  or do you just put them up to scare  people  yeah they actually work  never mind  i forgot we are in a walmart  just put the money in a plastic sack or  something  oh and i want you to fart in a tube with  that dirty  butt not because it's my fetish or  anything i just want you to do it don't  judge me  oh  what's the hold up  i want to escape before some crazy  [ __ ] call 911.  it looks like the guy who came in before  me forgot to refill the cash registers  what does that mean  can i still have free money  there's nothing here will there be  anything else i can't help you with  today sir  it's not real gun i only wanted to see  how you would react i'm filming a silly  tick tock or whatever kids are doing  nowadays  oh yeah then where is your buddy with a  camera  that's none of your business [ __ ]  hey i was wondering  have any young kids walked in here  recently you know under the age of 10 or  so  well a mom walked in about 20 minutes  ago with her kid but i don't know why  you need to that kind of information  look we're both guys here i'm sure you  know exactly what i'm talking about  oh i know exactly what you're saying  haha go and get some if you know what i  mean the kids on dial number eight  hey manic doesn't that look like feral  over there to you what are you talking  about bro that can't be feral he can't  be within 10 miles of us since mom and  uncle chuck filed that restraining order  for trying to break into our house last  year to try and kidnap me wait i think  that is farrell what is he doing  what the hell was that did you just take  a photo of my kid's ass sorry my flash  was on you know my son is only three  years old right yeah that's why i meant  to turn the flash off [ __ ]  i'm calling the police i'd like to see  you try karen  [Applause]  mama  damn i'm hungry daddy needs some lace  potato chips  sir i am going to need you to take those  potato chips out of your coat right now  what do you mean i didn't steal [ __ ] you  are just being racist sir i was watching  the whole thing do you have any idea who  you are speaking to  no my name is farrell the master thief  of moby is i'm the father of manic the  hedgehog who the [ __ ] is that well give  me some time and i will explain you know  what planet mobius is right  no well planet mobius is where i'm from  my son manic the hedgehog is the prince  of that whole [ __ ] planet which makes  me king i'm basically earth's equivalent  of martin luther king jr adolf hitler or  michael jackson after he became white  damn yeah i know sir i am going to need  you to end over the bag of chips or else  you'll have to leave the store  farrell are you using your position as  my foster father to get power over  others you're damn right  but that's so wrong  no what's wrong is that gay marriage is  still legal in this country  now do you want to watch me as i go over  there and steal from that kid in the  wheelchair  hey let go these are my chips help me  thief  hey you're that kid that we saw outside  but why do you have a black eye after  you guys left my big brother tried to  rape me i was barely able to get away  from him by rolling into moving traffic  but not before he punched me in the face  and pooped in my mouth well you had  better hand over the chips before i  raped your cute little ass instead white  [Music]  boy really feral again  oh great not you again are we really  doing this  you know when i first walked into the  store and i asked you where the little  boys were at i thought we were on the  same page i was on the same page as you  when you talked about stalking kids  [ __ ] kids in their ass that's fine by  me but when you come in and you start  stealing my bags of chips now that's  where i draw the line  oh come on  come on austin i thought we were friends  we're not friends and don't you dare  call me austin and you know what else i  already called the cops on your ass the  moment you walked into the store i'm not  as [ __ ] as you think i am  [Music]  you're under arrest put your hands up  please don't arrest my foster father he  hasn't stolen anything he already gave  the chips back  you're right he hasn't stolen anything  cause he [ __ ] [ __ ]  manic my boy i gotta tell you something  i'm not as good as you think i am i was  never the master thief of mobius why do  you think we have only ever stolen from  crippled people it's cause i'm not good  enough to go after normal people  but with that said  i ain't going to jail tonight  oh my god let that kid go feral  pharaoh stop it's not worth it  shut up any of you take another step  forward and i'm blowing this kid's ball  off  now i'm going to calmly walk out this  door do you understand and force him to  make me a grilled cheese sandwich do you  understand  damn it this is bad if only sonic the  hedgehog's boyfriend bartlett be  montclair of dresden the richest sexiest  and strongest man alive was here to save  us all  turn around buddy this party is only for  special guests i'm afraid that i can't  let you in  special guests you say  that's what i said only members of the  five are allowed beyond this door so get  the [ __ ] away before i toss you up  myself  look pal i don't think you know exactly  who you're dealing with here  so move out away [ __ ] i'm here for the  high rise party up in this [ __ ] i don't  think so how about you go take that  elevator down instead before i lose my  temper with your ass  quiet your mouth  nobody talks in such a way to bus driver  bob not even you  but driver gob i didn't even recognize  you please come right in sorry for the  inconvenience and enjoy the refreshments  there are milk and cookies over on the  counter  bus driver bob i'm delighted to see you  could make it  come along take a seat the party has  just begun and the night is still young  did you say bus driver there is no way  in hell he is among the five richest  people on earth someone threw him out  hey hey don't you go sleeping on bus  driver bob nathan drake  this man you are looking at is none  other than the manager for the world  famous  doodlebops wash it it ain't nothing i'm  only the third richest man on planet  earth haha  so how of the reds have you been growing  your fortunes recently  i just sold my pair of golden guns for  29 billion dollars and when i also  discovered the ancient city of el dorado  oh yes i remember purchasing the golden  city of el dorado from you last week  with the change in my pockets because i  was bored  i really must thank you excuse for  providing us with these country  expensive gametes i'm sure they're  especially comfortable even for bus  driver bob's fat ass  thanks they cost around 200 000 bucks  each  that's all i can see why you're the  fifth richest man on earth and not the  fourth uh huh  [Music]  [Music]  what's that does that walmart building  over there have a faulty light bulb or  some [ __ ]  [Music]  that's not a faulty light bulb that is  morse code somebody most likely my [ __ ]  appears to be in some kind of distress  richest people of earth follow me we  strike before the simmering sun rises  this is my last resort  [Music]  [Music]  but i will  [Music]  i'll [ __ ] kill you i'll kill all of  you  manic my boy you better watch your ass  cause the moment i get out of jail i'm  coming for you next  your petty threats of violence mean  nothing to us feral do you want to know  why because love is more powerful than  hate  that's right pharaoh you can hate me and  my friends all you want but we will  always love you and hope that you get  the help that you need  yes we all forgive you this day police  please do us all a favor and take this  man away to prison  shut up all of you just shut the [ __ ] up  manic my boy you son of a [ __ ] you  traitor i trusted you to be my [ __ ]  i wish i never told that stupid rat guy  to kidnap you when you were a baby  come on sibs no everybody  let's show pharaoh how strong love can  be when we all come together  [Applause]  christ  [Applause]  [Music]  jesus  [Applause]  [Music]  [Applause]  [Music]  [Applause]  [Music]  [Applause]  [Music]  [Music]  is  [Applause]  gonna talk about things  [Music]  [Applause]  [Music]  [Applause]  [Music]  [Applause]  trees  [Applause]  [Music]  [Applause]  [Music]  [Applause]  please tell me  [Music]  [Applause]  [Music]